<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plinth Analytics</title>
    <link>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Plinth Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/blog/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/blog/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Plinth</title>
      <link>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>Plinth was co-founded by Kieran Mace, PhD and Nathaniel Phillips, PhD – two scientific leaders at the intersection of Pharma, RWD generation, and Data Science, who have dedicated their careers to realizing RWD’s potential to deliver value to the life sciences.
With leadership experience developing RWD products from medical records, and leveraging that RWD in the pharmaceutical industry, we created Plinth to empower life science teams to efficiently and robustly translate RWD into business value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact us</title>
      <link>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact us at info@plinthanalytics.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles</title>
      <link>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/principles/</guid>
      <description>All of our products are built according to 3 rigorous principles:
Business use-case driven
Our products begin and end with a business use-case. We need to know what pain points your business is facing and how a product could help solve it.
Built for humans
Our products are built to be used, and re-used by humans. This means we would rather create a product that is easy to use but specific in focus, than one that is hard to use but broad in focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Products</title>
      <link>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://silly-haupia-2459d1.netlify.app/products/</guid>
      <description>Focii Pressure Testing
Tools to evaluate RWD for quality and use-case suitability, enabling you to catch key limitations and warning signs early.
Analysis Ready Data (ARD)
Intentionaly curated, analysis ready data derived from raw data. Unlike raw data, analysis ready data contain only the patients and data relevant to your analysis and ready for immediate use in any analytics tool.
Analytics
Fit-for-purpose data analytics, comprised of summary and statistical analyses, both in tables and and visualizations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
